

Profile

I have 10 years of experience in developing web application.

At the First, I have developed web site by using PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Html, CSS.

I have specialized in developing shopping site, blog site, social manage system etc.

For the several years, I have studied all kind of JS language such as React JS, Angular JS, Vue JS and MongoDB, Express etc.

Recently, I'm developing web application with MERN Stack.

I'm trying to become a good MERN Stack developer and I'm working remotely.

And also, I'm interested in windows application and mobile device control.

Employment History

Notion at Software developer, Denmark

January 2018 — June 2022

I have been working as a MERN Stack developer.

And also, I'm developing windows application and device control program (PLC).

M2soft at Software Engineering, California

August 2013 — June 2017

I had developed Crownix Chart library with MFC/JDK/OpenGL.

I had developed several shopping site, blog site by using PHP framework.

Education

Bachelor's degree, IT University of Copenhagen, Copenhagen

June 2008 — August 2012

The IT University of Copenhagen is a public university and research institution in Copenhagen, the capital of Denmark. It is specialized in the multidisciplinary study of information technology within computer science, business IT and digital design.

I graduated and got Bachelor's degree

Details

Skrivergade 1, st.2850 Vildbjerg, Herning Municipality, Danish, 4518570523

k.james.dev@gmail.com

Skills

PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Html, CSS

C++, C#

OpenCV

Crypto system

React JS

MongoDB

jQuery

Express

Node JS

Next JS

Java

Mobile app development

Objective-C

Swift

Mobile game development

Embed System

Languages

English

Hobbies

Playing billiards and golf.

Solving mathematics problems.